[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What was the first MCU movie released?",
        "correctAnswer": "Iron-Man",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Incredible Hulk",
            "Thor",
            "Captain America - The First Avenger"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which Stone does Thanos collect first?",
        "correctAnswer": "Power Stone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Time Stone",
            "Space Stone",
            "Mind Stone",
            "Reality Stone",
            "Soul Stone"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What year was Steve Rogers born?",
        "correctAnswer": "1918",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1970",
            "1939",
            "1914"
        ]
        
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "How many possible outcomes did Dr. Strange see in Infinity War?",
        "correctAnswer": "14,000,605",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1",
            "14,000,000",
            "14,600,005"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "How many times were the Infinity Stones used in Endgame?",
        "correctAnswer": "3",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "4"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What is Tony Stark's fathers name?",
        "correctAnswer": "Howard Stark",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Norman Stark",
            "Ned Stark",
            "Rob Stark"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which Stone does Thanos collect last?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mind Stone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Time Stone",
            "Space Stone",
            "Reality Stone",
            "Soul Stone",
            "Power Stone"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What is Hawkeye's alt ego?",
        "correctAnswer": "Clint Barton",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Legolas",
            "Robin Hood",
            "Oliver Queen"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What nickname does Tony give Thor?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pointbreak",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Strongest Avenger",
            "Odinson",
            "Zeus"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which movie did Nick Fury first appear in?",
        "correctAnswer": "Iron-Man",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Iron-Man 2",
            "Captain America",
            "Avengers: Endgame"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Who has the alter ego Rescue?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pepper Potts",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Happy Hogan",
            "Spider-Man",
            "Gamora"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "What is the name of Tony Starks AI after Jarvis?",
        "correctAnswer": "Friday",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Wednesday",
            "April",
            "Morgan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Who doesn't get blipped",
        "correctAnswer": "Ant-Man",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Spider-Man",
            "Black Panther",
            "Bucky",
            "Dr. Strange",
            "Drax"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Where is Thanos from?",
        "correctAnswer": "Titan",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Saturn",
            "Uranas",
            "Pluto"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Who's suit uses Pym Particles",
        "correctAnswer": "Ant-Man",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Black Panther",
            "Iron-Man",
            "Hulk"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Who adds the extra weapons to make War Machine?",
        "correctAnswer": "Justin Hammer",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Justin Beiber",
            "Justin Timberlake",
            "Justin Stark",
            "Justin Hartley",
            "Justin Long"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "Who can't weild Mjolnir?",
        "correctAnswer": "Loki",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Jane Foster",
            "Vision",
            "Steve Rogers",
            "Odin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "Which stone is also known as the Aether?",
        "correctAnswer": "Reality Stone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Time Stone",
            "Space Stone",
            "Mind Stone",
            "Soul Stone",
            "Power Stone"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "What game does Korg play in Avengers: Endgame?",
        "correctAnswer": "Fortnite",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Call of Duty",
            "Rock, paper, Scissors",
            "Snakes and ladders"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "Other than Iron-Man 3, which other movie does the Mandarin star?",
        "correctAnswer": "Shang Chi",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Avengers: Age of Ultron",
            "Iron-Man 2",
            "Captain America: Civil War"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "What is the Hulk's alter Ego",
        "correctAnswer": "Bruce Banner",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Bruce Wayne",
            "Eric Banner",
            "Bruce Banana"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "What is Iron-Mans daughters name?",
        "correctAnswer": "Morgan",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Montanna",
            "Salt",
            "Crystal"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "What Infinity Stone is used to create Vision?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mind Stone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Time Stone",
            "Space Stone",
            "Reality Stone",
            "Soul Stone",
            "Power Stone"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "What type of radiation created The Hulk?",
        "correctAnswer": "Gamma",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Nuclear",
            "Neutron",
            "Electromagnetic"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "Which actress plays Gamora?",
        "correctAnswer": "Zoe Saldana",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Karen Gillan",
            "Zendaya",
            "Awkwafina"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "Who is the voice actor for Groot?",
        "correctAnswer": "Vin Diesel",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Jason Statham",
            "Bruce Willis",
            "Samuel L Jackson"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "Which Spider-Man villian was did not appear in Spider-Man: No Way Home?",
        "correctAnswer": "New-Goblin",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Sandman",
            "Doc Ock",
            "Green Goblin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "Which Fantastic 4 member has appeared in the MCU?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mr Fantastic",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Invisible Woman",
            "The Thing",
            "The Human Torch"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "Which movie does Stan Lee cameo as Hugh Hefner",
        "correctAnswer": "Iron-Man",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Iron-Man 2",
            "Iron-Man 3",
            "Avengers"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "What is Black Panthers sisters name?",
        "correctAnswer": "Shuri",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Sharee",
            "Sharon",
            "Letitia"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "Where does Thanos perform the first snap?",
        "correctAnswer": "Wakanda",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "New York",
            "Sydney",
            "Titan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "Who does Clint Barton become after the Snap?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ronin",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Jeremy Renner",
            "Conan",
            "Rogue"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "How many rings does Shang Chi inherit from his father?",
        "correctAnswer": "10",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "2",
            "5",
            "132"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "Which character isn't at Tony Stark's funeral?",
        "correctAnswer": "Natasha Romanoff",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Bruce Banner",
            "Nick Fury",
            "Carol Danvers"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "What is the secret enemy organisation that infiltrates SHIELD?",
        "correctAnswer": "Hydra",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Gyardos",
            "Sword",
            "Arrow"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "Who has died the most?",
        "correctAnswer": "Dr Strange",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Loki",
            "Thanos",
            "Captain America"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "Who weilds the sword \"GODSLAYER\"",
        "correctAnswer": "Gamora",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Nebula",
            "Mantis",
            "Drax"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "Which character uses Yaka arrows?",
        "correctAnswer": "Yondu",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Hawkeye",
            "Iron-Man",
            "Falcon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "Who was the MCU's first villian",
        "correctAnswer": "Iron Monger",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Kill Monger",
            "Thanos",
            "Red Skull",
            "Whip Lash"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "What is the name of the fleet of Iron-Man soliders?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Iron Legion",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Ultron",
            "Iron-Men",
            "The Iron-Force"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "What is Black Panther's suit made out of?",
        "correctAnswer": "Vibranium",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Adamantium",
            "Titanium",
            "Cotton"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "What Army does Loki use to attack New York",
        "correctAnswer": "The Chitauri",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Asgard",
            "Martian",
            "Ice Giants"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "Which Stone game Captain Marvel her powers",
        "correctAnswer": "Space Stone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Mind Stone",
            "Soul Stone",
            "Reality Stone"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "What does Carol Danvers think her name is when she loses her memory?",
        "correctAnswer": "Vers",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Dan",
            "Karen",
            "Rambeau"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "Who does Black Panther hand the Infinity Gauntlet to in the Endgame battle?",
        "correctAnswer": "Spider-Man",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Captain Marvel",
            "Iron-Man",
            "Clint Barton"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "Which movie does Agent Coulson not appear in?",
        "correctAnswer": "Captain America",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Iron-Man",
            "Thor",
            "The Avengers"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "Which movie does Agent Maria Hill not appear in?",
        "correctAnswer": "Captain America: Civil War",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Avengers",
            "Avengers: Age of Ultron",
            "Avengers: Endgame"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "Which tribe challenges T'challa for the throne?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Jabari Tribe",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Mining Tribe",
            "The Merchant Tribe",
            "The Border Tribe"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "Which Stone lies in the Eye of Agamotto",
        "correctAnswer": "Time Stone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Mind Stone",
            "Space Stone",
            "Soul Stone"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "Which of these Avengers meets Nick Fury first?",
        "correctAnswer": "Carol Danvers",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Steve Rogers",
            "Tony Stark",
            "Clint Barton"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "Which Stone demands a sacrifice?",
        "correctAnswer": "Soul Stone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Power Stone",
            "Reality Stone",
            "Mind Stone"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "question": "Which Stone is also known as the Tesseract?",
        "correctAnswer": "Space Stone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Power Stone",
            "Reality Stone",
            "Mind Stone"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "question": "Who thinks they are invisible from moving slowly?",
        "correctAnswer": "Drax",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Groot",
            "Thor",
            "Loki"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "question": "Who plays the character Red Skull?",
        "correctAnswer": "Hugo Weaving",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Petter Cullen",
            "Shia LaBeouf",
            "Ian McKellen"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "question": "Who was the director of Iron-Man",
        "correctAnswer": "Jon Favreau",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Anthony Russo",
            "Joe Russo",
            "Taika Waititi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "question": "Who's suit has an \"Insta-Kill\" mode?",
        "correctAnswer": "Spider-Man",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Iron-Man",
            "Black Panther",
            "War Machine"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "question": "Which stone is given to the Collector to safe gaurd?",
        "correctAnswer": "Reality Stone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Space Stone",
            "Time Stone",
            "Soul Stone",
            "Space Stone",
            "Mind Stone"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "question": "Where is Storm-Breaker forged?",
        "correctAnswer": "Nidavellir",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Knowhere",
            "Xander",
            "Vormir"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "question": "What year did the Avengers time travel to New York in Avengers: Endgame?",
        "correctAnswer": "2012",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "2016",
            "2008",
            "2020"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "question": "What is Bruce Banner's secret to dealing with the Hulk in The Avengers?",
        "correctAnswer": "He's always Angry",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "He's always Hungry",
            "He's always Hangry",
            "Secret Potion"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "question": "What powers the first Iron-Man suit?",
        "correctAnswer": "Miniaturized Arc Reactor",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Solar Panels",
            "Tesla Batteries",
            "Portable Power Bank"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "question": "What type of core is poisoning Tony in Iron-Man 2",
        "correctAnswer": "Palladium",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Vibranium",
            "Badassium",
            "Helium"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "question": "Which suit is Tony working on at the start of Iron-Man 3",
        "correctAnswer": "MK 42",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "MK 4",
            "MK 23",
            "MK 50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "question": "What was War Machine rebranded to in Iron-Man 3",
        "correctAnswer": "Iron Patriot",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "America Man",
            "American Iron-Man",
            "War Patriot"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "question": "Who take over Stark Indutries from Tony?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pepper Potts",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Happy Hogan",
            "Aldrich Killian",
            "James Rhodes"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "question": "What is Tony STark's home address?",
        "correctAnswer": "10880 Malibu Point, 90265",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "42 Wallaby Way, Sydney",
            "1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, Washington, D.C.",
            "742 Evergreen Terrace, Springfield"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "question": "Which Las Vages Casino was the awards cermony held at in Iron-Man?",
        "correctAnswer": "Caesers Palace",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Bellagio Hotel & Casino",
            "MGM Grand",
            "The Venetian Las Vegas"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "question": "Which award was Tony Stark being award in Iron-Man",
        "correctAnswer": "Apogee Award",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Golden Globe",
            "Nobel Peace Prize",
            "Pulitzer Prize"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "question": "WHat is the name of the Missile Tony is tasked to build for Raza?",
        "correctAnswer": "Jericho",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Warhog",
            "Sarmat",
            "Tomahawk",
            "Trident",
            "Agni",
            "DeepStrike",
            "Hellfire",
            "Satan",
            "Brahmos"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "question": "What did Yinsen plug into the electro magnet to keep Tony Stark alive?",
        "correctAnswer": "A Car Battery",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "An Arc Reactor",
            "A Generator",
            "Solar Panels"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "question": "What was the main weapon on the first Iron-Man suit?",
        "correctAnswer": "Flame Thrower",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Arc Blaters",
            "Ion Blaster",
            "Lightsaber"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "question": "Why couldn't Iron-Monger fly as high as Iron-Man?",
        "correctAnswer": "Suit froze up",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Too heavy",
            "Not enough power",
            "Not enough fuel"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "question": "What does the \"S\" stand for in S.H.I.E.L.D?",
        "correctAnswer": "Strategic",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Super",
            "Successful",
            "Supportive",
            "Star",
            "Sincere",
            "Sensuous",
            "Stupendous",
            "Support",
            "Sacred",
            "Synergy",
            "Soaring",
            "Saintly"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "question": "What does the \"H\" stand for in S.H.I.E.L.D?",
        "correctAnswer": "Homeland",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Head",
            "Hammer",
            "Hood",
            "Hive",
            "Hand",
            "Heart",
            "Hook",
            "Hologram",
            "Humdinger",
            "Hydrophobic",
            "Halcyon",
            "Hypothermia"
            
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "question": "What does the \"I\" stand for in S.H.I.E.L.D?",
        "correctAnswer": "Intervention",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Inspiring",
            "Immediately",
            "Imagination",
            "Inventive",
            "Illegal",
            "Impactful",
            "Iron",
            "Imitate",
            "Institution",
            "Inclusive",
            "Innovative",
            "Invincible"
            
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "question": "What does the \"E\" stand for in S.H.I.E.L.D?",
        "correctAnswer": "Enforcement",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Empowering",
            "Enhancer",
            "Economical",
            "Electrifying",
            "Easygoing",
            "Enlightening",
            "Enriching",
            "Endorsing",
            "Enthusiastic",
            "Enchanting",
            "Euphoric",
            "Experienced"
            
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "question": "What does the \"L\" stand for in S.H.I.E.L.D?",
        "correctAnswer": "Logistics",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Loving",
            "Lifesaver",
            "Leader",
            "Luminous",
            "Lasting",
            "Legendary",
            "Lucrative",
            "Luxurious",
            "Loyal",
            "Lucky",
            "Lucid",
            "Logical"
            
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "question": "What does the \"D\" stand for in S.H.I.E.L.D?",
        "correctAnswer": "Division",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Dynamic",
            "Dutiful",
            "Devoted",
            "Dedicated",
            "Distinguished",
            "Desirable",
            "Dignified",
            "Decisive",
            "Delicious",
            "Determined",
            "Disciplined"
            
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 78,
        "question": "What is Odin's fathers name?",
        "correctAnswer": "Bor",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Gorr",
            "Mor",
            "Worr",
            "Lor"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 79,
        "question": "What make is the car Iron-Monger throws at Iron-Man?",
        "correctAnswer": "Audi",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "BMW",
            "Tesla",
            "Ferari"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 80,
        "question": "What is the MK 3 Iron-Man suit made of?",
        "correctAnswer": "Titanium",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Vibranium",
            "Iron",
            "Adamantium"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 81,
        "question": "How many days without incedents has Bruce had at the start of The Incredible Hulk",
        "correctAnswer": "158",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1",
            "100",
            "150"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "question": "What drink factory does Bruce Banner work at?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pingo Doce",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Coca Cola",
            "Fanta",
            "Mountain Dew"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 83,
        "question": "What is Bruce's username while talking with the secret scientist?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mr Green",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Big Green",
            "Green Boy",
            "Greeny"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 84,
        "question": "Who does Emil Blonksy become?",
        "correctAnswer": "Abomination",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Whip Lash",
            "Iron Monger",
            "Kill monger",
            "Mandarin",
            "Yellow Jacket"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 85,
        "question": "What heart rate triggers Bruce to turn into the Hulk",
        "correctAnswer": "200",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "250",
            "60",
            "100"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 86,
        "question": "Who does the Hulk throw a forklift at?",
        "correctAnswer": "Emil Blonksy",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Thor",
            "Thanos",
            "Thunderbolt Ross"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 87,
        "question": "What Colour is the Power Stone?",
        "correctAnswer": "Purple",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Red",
            "Yellow",
            "Orange",
            "Green",
            "Blue"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 88,
        "question": "What Colour is the Reality Stone?",
        "correctAnswer": "Red",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Yellow",
            "Orange",
            "Green",
            "Blue",
            "Purple"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 89,
        "question": "What Colour is the Mind Stone?",
        "correctAnswer": "Yellow",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Red",
            "Orange",
            "Green",
            "Blue",
            "Purple"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 90,
        "question": "What Colour is the Soul Stone?",
        "correctAnswer": "Orange",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Red",
            "Yellow",
            "Green",
            "Blue",
            "Purple"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 91,
        "question": "What Colour is the Time Stone?",
        "correctAnswer": "Green",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Red",
            "Yellow",
            "Orange",
            "Blue",
            "Purple"
        ]
    }
    ,{
        "id": 92,
        "question": "What Colour is the Space Stone?",
        "correctAnswer": "Blue",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Red",
            "Yellow",
            "Orange",
            "Green",
            "Purple"
        ]
    }

]
 
 
    ,{
        "id": ,
        "question": "",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    }

 
 
